Connor Vernon

Full-stack Developer

CAREER PROFILE

Computer science graduate (Cloud computing Major) with 2 years practical experience in programming and web design. Optimised SQL databases and developed programs to improve workflow efficiency for F1 Building Consultants. Passionate about web design and builds web applications during spare time.

EXPERIENCE

Full Stack Developer and administration

F1 Building Consultants | Balwyn North | January 2019 - Present

- Improving existing databases/software which has saved the company money and ensured builders across Victoria get their products on-time.
- Assisted with administration which has generated new IT solutions for the existing software such as automations to reduce human error

UX/UI Developer

Capstone Project | Deakin University - Burwood | March 2018 - October 2018

- Leading the dynamic front-end design using technologies such as Bootstrap 4 and CSS media queries to ensure compatibility on multiple devices.
- Working under strict deadlines using Scrum methodology to effectively meet deadlines and to reflect on improvements.

Front End Developer

IPAN (Placement) | Deakin University - Burwood | July 2018 – October 2018

- Conducting user panels and questionnaires on a target group (age 60+) which assisted with changing the design of the web prototypes.
- Designing high fidelity prototypes using the Adobe Creative Suite.

Food Service Attendant

Donvale Rehabilitation Hospital | Donvale | August 2017 – December 2018

- Nominated for the employee of the month through great customer service and putting the customer first.
- Using strong communication and teamwork skills to ensure a ward of 90+ patients got their correct meals in short-time constraints.

+61 450 876 767 connor.j.vernon97@gmail.com conjamver.github.io/portfolio linkedin.com/in/cjvernon github.com/conjamver

SKILLS

Front-end	Back-end
HTML5	PHP
CSS3/SASS	MySQL
javaScript	Node.js
Bootstrap	Express.js
ReactJS	AJAX
jQuery	Git

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Computer Science

Deakin University – Burwood 2016 – 2018

EXTRACURRICULAR

SoloLearn and Udemy (2017 – 2020)

Explored online courses which have enhanced my fundamental programming skills. Succeeded to create a live website from these experiences.

Leading a rock band (2016 - 2018)

Lead a rock band with 4 other members as the vocalist. Involved organising rehearsals and gigs. Performed 5 live shows and recorded 2 songs.